export default data = [
  {
      question: "The new stadium was built at a convenient ______ , close to an MRT station and within walking distance to a popular shopping center.",
      options: ["vacancy","procedure","residence","location"],
      correct_option: "location"
  },
  {
      question: "The young Taiwanese pianist performed ______ well and won the first prize in the music contest.",
      options: ["intimately","remarkably","potentially","efficiently"],
      correct_option: "remarkably"
  },
  {
      question: "As thousands of new ______ from Southeastern Asia have moved to Taiwan for work or marriage, we should try our best to help them adjust to our society.",
      options: ["immigrants","messengers","possessors","agencies"],
      correct_option: "immigrants"
  },
  {
      question: "Although the manager apologized many times for his poor decision, there was nothing he could do to ______ his mistake.",
      options: ["resign","retain","refresh","remedy"],
      correct_option: "remedy"
  },
  {
      question: "Last winter’s snowstorms and freezing temperatures were quite ______ for this region where warm and short winters are typical.",
      options: ["fundamental","extraordinary","statistical","individual"],
      correct_option: "extraordinary"
  },
  {
      question: "To overcome budget shortages, some small schools in rural areas have set up ______ programs to share their teaching and library resources.",
      options: ["cooperative","objective","relative","infinitive"],
      correct_option: "cooperative"
  },
  {
      question: "After spending much time carefully studying the patient’s ______ , the doctor finally made his diagnosis.",
      options: ["confessions","symptoms","protests","qualifications"],
      correct_option: "symptoms"
  },
  {
      question: "The universe is full of wonders. Throughout history, people have been ______ by the mystery of what lies beyond our planet.",
      options: ["notified","complicated","fascinated","suspended"],
      correct_option: "fascinated"
  },
  {
      question: "The president’s speech will be broadcast ______ on television and radio so that more people can listen to it at the time when it is delivered.",
      options: ["comparatively","temporarily","simultaneously","permanently"],
      correct_option: "simultaneously"
  },
  {
      question: "In order to expand its foreign market, the company decided to ______ its products and provide more varieties to the customer.",
      options: ["exceed","dismiss","retrieve","diversify"],
      correct_option: "diversify"
  },
]